Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES VII. Minutes, 1935-39, 1957-81
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VIII. FOREIGN
  - Foreign
    - L
      - Lebanon 1955-72 (Box 204, Folder 21)
    - M
      - Malaya (Malaysia)
        - 1955-71 (Box 204, Folder 22)
        - 1975 (Box 204)
      - Malta 1956-67 (Box 204, Folder 23)
      - Mauritius 1958-68 (Box 204, Folder 24)
      - Malaysia, Perak, Family Planning Association 1965-70 (Box 204, Folder 25)
      - Mexico
        - Correspondence
          - 1963-74 (Box 204, Folder 26)
          - 1975 (Box 204)
          - 1955-62 (Box 204, Folder 27)
        - General 1958-70 (Box 204, Folder 28)
        - U.S.-Mexico Border Conference 1961-66 (Box 204, Folder 29)
    - N
      - New Guinea 1955-65 (Box 204, Folder 30)
      - New Zealand 1955-73 (Box 204, Folder 31)
      - Norway 1962-66 (Box 204, Folder 32)
    - P
      - Pakistan, Correspondence 1960-70 (Box 204, Folder 33)
      - Panama, (Canal Zone) 1955-69 (Box 204, Folder 34)
      - Philippines
        - 1956-70 (Box 204, Folder 35)
        - 1975-77 (Box 204)
      - Poland, Correspondence 1959-69 (Box 204, Folder 36)
      - Puerto Rico
        - Correspondence
          - 1958-71 (Box 204, Folder 37)
          - 1977-79 (Box 204)
        - IPPF/PPFA, The Situation 1973 (Box 204, Folder 38)
        - Zalduondo, Celestina, Family Planning Association, Correspondence 1961-70 (Box 204, Folder 39)
        - Birth Control Situation, Legal 1939, 1954-67 (Box 204, Folder 40)
        - Reports 1954-67 (Box 204, Folder 41)
        - Zaluondo, Working Papers and Talk 1958-61 (Box 204, Folder 42)
    - Russia 1958-62 (Box 204, Folder 43)
    - S
      - Scotland 1959-64 (Box 204, Folder 44)
      - Singapore
        - 1967-69 (Box 204, Folder 45)
        - 1955-66 (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - South America
        - General, Correspondence 1960-72 (Box 205, Folder 2)
        - Argentina, Correspondence 1955-74 (Box 205, Folder 3)
        - British, Guiana, Correspondence 1954-59 (Box 205, Folder 4)
        - Chile 1962-73 (Box 205, Folder 5)
        - Columbia, Correspondence
          - 1964-73 (Box 205, Folder 6)
          - 1977 (Box 205)
        - Peru 1955-71 (Box 205, Folder 7)
        - Venezuela 1955-71 (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Spain 1959, 1963-67 (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - Sweden
        - Correspondence
          - 1955, 1959-69 (Box 205, Folder 10)
          - Ottesen-Jensen, Mrs. Elise 1954-67 (Box 205, Folder 11)
      - Switzerland, Correspondence 1955-70 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - T
      - Thailand
        - 1955, 1962-74 (Box 205, Folder 13)
        - Dr. Sangad Plengvanj, Trip 1963-64 (Box 205, Folder 14)
        - Nurses' Family Planning, Scholarships 1964 (Box 205, Folder 15)
      - Turkey, Correspondence 1955, 1962-72 (Box 205, Folder 16)
      - Tunisia 1964-66 (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - Uruguay 1955-69 (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - Virgin Islands
      - PP
        - 1964-73 (Box 205, Folder 19)
        - 1979 (Box 205)
      - General, Correspondence 1956-67 (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - West Indies
      - General, Correspondence 1955-68 (Box 205, Folder 21)
      - Barbados, Correspondence 1954-74 (Box 205, Folder 22-23)
      - Jamaica
        - Family Planning Association 1965-72 (Box 205, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence 1955-69 (Box 205, Folder 25)
      - Barbados, Field Trips 1954-65 (Box 205, Folder 26)
      - Trinidad, Correspondence 1956-69 (Box 205, Folder 27)
    - Yugoslavia 1964-66 (Box 205, Folder 28)
- SERIES IX. GUTTMACHER
  - Publications
    - Abortion 1970 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Annotated List of Published Reports, Clinical Trials with Contraceptives 1959 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - Artifizielle Insemination 1969 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - Biographical Notes on Same Famous Conjoined Twins 1967 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Bootlegging Bodies 1955 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Caesarean Section in Twin Pregnancy 1962 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Compound and Complex, Presentation Assoc. with Plural Births 1962 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Concentrated Oxytocin Solution for Therapeutic Interruption of Miotrimester Pregnancy 1962 (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Contraception Control: Its Implications for the Individual and World 1961 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - Conception Control and the Medical Profession 1947 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - Contraception 1968 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - The Contraception Problem 1967 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - A Critical Study of the Efficacy of Jelly as a Contraceptive 1952 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Medical Aspects of Human Sexuality 1968 (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Early Attitudes Towards Infertility 1953 (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - Effectiveness of Preceptin 1954 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - Factors Affecting Normal Expectancy of Conception 1956 (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - Factors in Decline in Incidence and Severity, undated (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - Family Planning, A Challenge to Health Workers of Every Nation 1969 (Box 101, Folder 43)
    - Family Planning, The Needs and Methods 1958 (Box 101, Folder 44)
    - The First Five Years, Obstetric Report of the Mt. Sinai Hospital, N.Y. 1952 (Box 101, Folder 45)
    - Fertility of Man 1958 (Box 101, Folder 46)
    - Fetal Electrocardiography 1958 (Box 101, Folder 47)
    - The Fetus of Multiple Gestations (Box 101, Folder 48)